Guide to the Eric M. and Carol L. Meyers papers, 1970-2019 UA.29.02.0027
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2019.0076, 1
  - Sepphoris, 1.6
    - Duke Archive Drawings, Book 1: Inking Sheets; 2000 Drawings; Pencil and Inkings Sheets (Box 42)
    - Archived drawings (Box 43)
      3 3-ring binders
    - Large index cards (most with drawing and/or photo) with pottery registration data from JSP 1985-1989: pottery from areas 95.1, 94.1, and 84.4, 3 items 3 packets (Box 44)
    - Large index cards with pottery registration data (most with drawing and/or photo from JSP 1985-1989: 1. pottery from Area 84.2; 2. and 3. pottery from Areas 85.1 and 84.1 (Box 44)
      3 boxes
    - Photo logs (color and B/W) for the 10 excavation seasons (Box 44)
      10 sets
    - 2-volume set of Sepphoris III: The Architecture, Stratigraphy, and Artifacts of the Western Summit of Sepphoris, 2018 (Box 45)
    - Sepphoris I: The Pottery from Ancient Sepphoris, 2013 (Box 45)
      1 copy
    - Sepphoris II: Clay lamps from Ancient Sepphoris, 2016 (Box 45)
    - News clippings (JSP 1985, 1986, 1989) (Box 45)
      3 folders
    - News clippings (SRP 1993, 1994, 1996, 1997), 1993-1997 (Box 45)
    - "Mona Lisa of the Galilee," North Carolina Museum of Art (Box 45)
      1 video tape
    - Stuart Miller (U. Conn.) lecture on "Sepphoris in Talmudic Literature" (Box 45)
      1 audio tape
    - Administrative matters (correspondence, grants, permits, affiliations, etc.) (Box 45)
      17 folders
    - "Mona Lisa", 1987-1988 (Box 46)
      1 legal-size expanded folder with flap and cord
    - Black and white photos: field shots (Box 46)
      5 3-ring binders
    - Black and white photos: field shots (Box 47)
      6 3-ring binders
    - Sepphoris 35 mm slides: objects, small finds (JSP, SRP, SAE) (Box 48)
    - Sepphoris 35mm slides: triclinium, Dionysos mosaic carpet (JSP), 1987-1988 (Box 48)
    - Sepphoris 35 mm slides general subjects, photos & drawings (JSP &SRP) (Box 48)
    - Various drawings: multi-unit plans, glass fragments and vessels, miscellaneous, objects (mostly metal), incense shovels, plans of 2011 season, unit plans, stepped pools (incomplete),underground installations, baulk drawings (incomplete; see those in 3-ring binders), Larry Belkin's plans & studies before conservation planned for National Park, miqveh (ritual bath) reconstruction drawings with humans (by Anna Iamim) (Box 48)
      11 folders
    - Field Shots: SRP 1993-1994, 1996-1997; SAE 2000, 1993-2000 (Box 49)
    - Field Shots: JSP, 1985-1989 (Box 49)
    - Dionysos mosaic black and white photos and color negatives (Box 49)
    - B/W/O objects: SRP, 1993-1994, 1996-1997; SAE 2000, 1993-2000 (Box 49)
    - JSP 1988 color negatives and prints (Box 49)
    - Black and white and color candids (1993, 1994, 1996, 1997, 2000), 1993-2000 (Box 49)
    - Contacts of objects and pottery, by Hebrew university photographer (Box 49)
      1 binder
    - Sepphoris section (balk) drawings, etc. (Box 50)
    - Large index cards with pottery registration data (most with drawing and/or photo) from JSP 1985–1989; 1: pottery from Locus 84.1068 (cistern fill); 2: 1. pottery from Area 84.2 (Box 50)
      2 boxes
    - SAP 2000, B/W-SS 1, 2 (Box 50)
    - Photographs: miqva'ot (ritual baths); stone vessels (Box 50)
      1 small padded mailer with discs of photos
    - Photos of Hebrew University areas of excavation (Box 50)
    - Prints of pottery plates 1-32 for SEPPHORIS I) _ disc with drawings of pls. 1-36 and Nabratein (Box 50)
    - Pottery readings for JSP, 1985-1986 (Box 50)
      1 3-hole folder
    - Unidentified prints and negatives (Box 50)
      1 twin-pocket folder
    - Drawings (SEPPHORIS I, pottery plates 1-33, 37-54; drawings for object plates) (Box 50)
    - Metal analysis (Box 50)
    - Inscribed materials (including some photos) (Box 50)
    - 12 coins from Sepphoris (Box 50)
      1 clasp envelope, coins ceded to Duke University (July 19, 1995); with documentation
    - Pottery plates 43-51; original drawings for SEPPHORIS I (Box 51)
      1 roll
    - Miscellaneous drawings (Box 51)
    - Flora and fauna samples (Box 52)
      1 Styrofoam box
    - Eric Lapp's 2005 notes for lamp volume (Sepphoris II) (Box 52)
      1 black notebook
    - Some registration cards (Xeroxes), and Eric Lapp's notes for Sepphoris II (Box 52)
  - Oversize and rolled materials
    - Oversize maps and drawings of excavation sites (Oversize-folder 6)
    - Oversize maps and drawings of excavation sites (Oversize-folder 7)
    - Oversize maps and drawings of excavation sites (Oversize-folder 8)
    - Poster of the "Mona Lisa of Galilee" (Sepphoris mosaic) (Oversize-folder 8)
    - Oversize maps and drawings of excavation sites (Oversize-folder 9)
    - Rolled oversize drawings (Box 53)